Guide to the Edward A. Feigenbaum Papers SC0340
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Original accession, Accession ARCH-1986-052
  - Project files
    - Way Cognitive Science. "A Very Personal History" by G. A. Miller from Talk to Cognitive Science Workshop, MIT, 1 June 1979.and "Historical Addendum" (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Distributed Problem Solving: "Multiprocessor Organization--A Survey." P.H. Enslow Jr. from Computing Surveys, March 1977. HPP-78-2 "Issues in Distributed Sensor Net Design" R. G. Smith. Jan. 1978 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Winograd, CS/Ling 365, Winter 1978: Course material for "Seminar in Computational Linguistics" and copies of readings. (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Humberto Maturana: Notes on Maturana as guest speaker. "Knowledge and Social Sciences: a preliminary analysis" D.T. Campbell, T.F. Pettigrew, S.E. Taylor, T.I. Mimica,May '77. "The Cybernetics of Cognitive Processes" K.L. Wilson May '74. "Biology of Cognition" Humberto Maturana. Nov. 1970. "Autopoiesis" XV H. Maturana. "Problems of Knowledge and Cognizing Organisms" F. Varela and E. von Glasersfeld. April 1977. "Biology of Language: the epistemology of reality". "Representations of Autonomy" (Working Draft) J. Goguen and F. Varela, Aug. 1977. (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - CS 209--Flores: Notes and readings for CS 209 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Pribram 1977: Various notes and reading material (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Representational Semantics CS 365, Winograd, Spring 1977: Notes and outlines for course. (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Notes from IJCAI-5 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Copies of "Meta-knowledge and Memory" A. Barr, with requests for corrections/ suggestions. Returned copies and comments from various sources. (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Copies of: "The Computer and the Brain" John von Neumann "Production Systems: Models of Control Structures" A. Newell "The Role of Raw Power in Intelligence" H. Moravec, 1976 "KRS--Chap. 1 (draft)" Brian Smith, 1977 Course Description, CS 365--Seminar in Computational Linguistics, Spr 1977. Winograd "Sentence Perception as an Interactive Parallel Process" William Marslen-Wilson, July 1975 "Lambda: The Ultimate Declarative" G.L. Steele Jr. 1976 "Lambda: The Ultimate Imperative" G.L. Steele Jr. and G.J. Sussman 1976 "In Defence of Logic (draft)" P.J. Hayes "Reasoning about knowledge and action" R. Moore. "The Semantic Conception of Truth" A. Tarski "The Representation of Semantic Knowledge" G. Hendrix "A Formalism for Modelling" H. Levesque et al. "A Theory of English Grammar" B. Martin, 19 76 "Some Philosophical Problems from the Standpoint of Artificial Intelligence" J. McCarthy and P.J. Hayes (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - ARPA Contract 1977 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - ARPA Management Report 1979 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - 2FLZ 754 ARPA MDA903-80-C-0107: cover letter for revised cost estimate of HPP, 1980. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - New ARPA Proposal: for "Knowledge Base Management System" July 1979. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Copy of HPP proposal, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - HPP ARPA Projects- Consolidation Efforts. Encloses 3 folders: EAF- ARPA Meeting, July 23-24, 1974; EAF--ARPA Correspondence, re:contract costs, retro-active approval of expenses; ARPA Consolidation: various notes and correspondence (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 2 FCZ 723 ONR N00014-81-K-0303 Intelligent Agents request and approval for increased funding (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Intelligent Agents Proposal -- 1980: Includes copy of proposal, "ISI Research into Cooperative Interactive Systems" by W. Mark, L.Lingard, D. Wilczynski (1980). Copy of notes for presentation of same, budget proposal for Intelligent Agents Project, and draft of proposal (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Intelligent Agents: notes and correspondence regarding project, copy of "ISI Research in the Area of Cooperative Interactive Systems" (1979),and "An anatomy of Graceful Interaction in Spoken and Written Man-Machine Communication" P. Hayes and R. Reddy (1979) (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - MSC 79-05998 The Mechanization of Formal Reasoning. Correspondence re: extension of proposal, grant renewal; and copy of NSF proposal (1982). (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - 2 FCZ 713 ONR N00014-81-K-0004: Letter from Arthur M. Diness (Assoc. Dir. of Research, Engineering Sciences, DB6ept. of the Navy) to E. A. Feigenbaum re: possible underequipped for project. April 16, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Semi-annual Technical Report for Contract Period Aug. 1, 1977 to Jan. 31, 1978 and 2 copies of "Final Technical Report... Aug. 1, 1973 through July 31, 1977." (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Proposal to the National Science Foundation: The Automation of Scientific Inference: Heuristic Computing Applied to Protein Crystallography. 3/1977--2/1979 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Proposal: MOLGEN--A Computer Science Application to MolecularGenetics (NSF Grant MCS 76-11649) (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - ONR Distribution--quarterly progress reports list (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - (N00014-81-K-0004): request for funding modification, 1/1982 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - ONR: quarterly management reports from Office of Naval Research, 12/80 -4/82, request from Buchanan to revise budget (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - (2 P41 RR000785-09 NIH): SUMEX award notices for 1981 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - (3 P41 RR000785-0852 NIH [SUMEX]): notice of grant award 1981 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Xerox EOS. Information from Xerox on new Xerox 1100, 6/81 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Xerox Contract. Contract for Feigenbaum to work as consultant for Xerox, 7/80. (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - VM Project: Ventilator Manager notes, reprint "Computer-based Medical Decision Making: From MYCIN to VM", L. Fagan, E. Shortliffe, and B. Buchanan, 1980. (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - VLSI. Proposal to DARPA for a Network-Based Graphical Design System, 7/79, notes on discussion for choosing graphics interface, presentation notes for HPP-VLSI project 12/79 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Robotics: Copy of Businessweek (6/9/80) article "Robots join the labor force" (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - ONR Proposal 1980: The Development of Representation Methods to Facilitate Knowledge Acquisition and Exposition in Expert Systems (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - (2 FCZ 703 MDA903-80-C-0107 VLSI/CAD): Modification of contract for VLSI/CAD project, quarterly management report for HPP, March 31, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - ONR Panel: List of Names for ONR/NRC Panel on Applied Mathematics (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - NLM Proposal: Blum. Proposal to Dept. of Health and Human Services, Oct. 1982 Computer Acquisition/Representation of Medical Knowledge (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - NSF Advisory Committee: Correspondence, minutes and press release re: NSF Advisory Subcommitte on Computing, 1980-81. (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - NSF Computer Engineering Division: Copy of report "Grants Supported by the Computer Engineering Program in Fiscal Year 1981 and 1982" and map with general distribution of awards. (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - NSF Student Science Programs: guide for preparation of proposals, 1980. (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - HPP Miscellaneous, three folders and loose notes: Principal Investigators--Information: copy of article on accounting problems on grants between universities and fed, and office memo reviewing federal export regulations. Intelligent Terminal Proposal: notes on intelligent couplers and bulletin board, 1974. Terminal Theft: correspondence, invoices and purchase requisitions re: theft of two terminals 6/75. Loose Papers: memo on space for HPP personnel (7/16/76) and memo re: deficit on NIH grant. (7/19/76). (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - IBM Proposal: Attempts to determine the User's conceptualizations of task domains within Intelligent Tutoring Systemsÿ. 1/25/83, Buchanan - Principal investigator (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - (2FCZ 439 MCS81-17330 NSF CRYSALIS): Copy of final project report for CRYSALIS (12/7/82); correspondence on project, and outline of system design (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - NIH Guide for Grants and Contracts 1980 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - (5PO1 LM03395 NAT. LIB. MED.): Office memo and notice of grant award for "Research Program: Biomedical Knowledge Representation" for 1981 and 1982. (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - (2 FCZ 426 5PO1LM03395-03 NLM NIH): empty (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - NLM Continuation Proposal 1980: continuation application for Computer Acquisition/ Representation of Medical Knowledge and request for rebudgeting. (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - (1 FCZ 610 Schlumberger-Doll): Memo on transfer of funds ($1500) to Prof. Feigenbaum's unrestricted fund, Nov. 22, 1980. (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - (1 FCZ 618 HPP GIFT FUND [EMYCIN]): memo on gift of $2000 from EAF to HPP gift fund. (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - (MDA-903-80-C-0680 DARPA): office memos on administration of HPP, quarterly management reports on VLSI/ CAD Network Based Graphics Development (April and July 1982) (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Biomedical Knowledge Engineering and Infectious Diseases, submitted to NIH May, 1977. (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Proposal: ARPA Heuristic Programming Project (ARPA Contract MDA 903-77-C-0322) Feb 1977, E. Feigenbaum principal investigator (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Proposal to the National Institute of Health: A Computer-Based Consultant for Medical Decision Making 2/24/77. (Labeled inactive) (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Proposal to the NIH: Computer-Based Consultations in Clinical Therapeutics 1977. (Labeled inactive) (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - CRYSALIS: Progress report May 1977; budget projection Feb 1, 1975 - Jan 31, 1977; invitation to EAF to speak at chemical crystallography seminar of National Academy of Sciences-Nat'l Research Council, Sep 1975; revised budget for CRYSALIS, March 1976. (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - MOLGEN (#1): copies of continuation proposal for MOLGEN, March 1979 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - MOLGEN (#2): Letter to Prof. Lederberg from John R. Pasta of NSF, thanking him for site visit (Mar 1977); Revised notice of grant award, Feb 1981; request for information on using DENDRAL and Meta-DENDRAL for identification of drugs from E.F. Domino, M.D. (Mar 1981); printout of draft of MOLGEN project report for NIH (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - MOLGEN (#3): Draft proposal by Mark Stefik for MOLGEN (May 76); printout of MOLGEN archive by Stefik (Jan 78), Printout on MOLGEN, Oct 75, addressed to EAF from Stefik; MOLGEN notes, printout Sep 77; memo re: MOLGEN grant (May 76) (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - MYCIN: copy of note on MYCIN's question-answering ability (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - ARPA P.I. Meeting, L.A., Feb 6-8, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - ARPA P.I. Meeting, March 1975 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - ARPA: contains folder on ARPA Contractor's Meeting, San Diego, Feb. 1971 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Proposal for Continuation of the Stanford Artificial Intelligence Project and Heuristic DENDRAL Project ARPA SD-183, June 1969 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - VM "Ventilator Manager": copy of article "Managing the Data for Respiratory Measurements" by John J. Osborn, M.D. (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - ARPA PI Meeting: notes from meeting, probably early 70's (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - ARPA Contractors Meeting: San Diego, Feb. 1971 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - ARPA Contractors Meeting: San Diego, March 12-14, 1975. (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - ARPA Contractors Meeting: Washington D.C., Dec 1971 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - ARPA EAF: Revised Proposal to Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency for the continuation of the Heuristic Programming Project and the VLSI Theory Project. May 1982 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - EPAM Vocabulary List/ EPAM Inverse List (8-22-61) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - "EPAMELTON" runs (EPAM Hypothesis for Melton, Shepherd and Teghtsoonian running recognition experiments) Prop. of N. Zvegintzov and E. A. Feigenbaum (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - EPAM III run, June 1963 (?) for Zvegintzov (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Max Allen--Theses work. Handwritten copy of program, printout of program, printout of EPAM run (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - EPAM III--2 notes on changes to program, log book, summaries (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports June 1977 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports December 1974 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports September 1974 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports January 1975 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports August 1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports July 1973 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports September 1974 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - "Semantics in Conceptual Analysis" (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports April 1970 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports May 1970 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports April 1970 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports March 25, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports March 6, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports March 5, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports July 1974 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports November 1978 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports October 17, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports April 1970 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports June 1969 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports August 1969 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports January 1970 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports December 24, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports June 9, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports September 22, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports September 25, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports March 14, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - AI Lab Memos and Computer Science Reports June 1968 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - DENDRAL (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - NASA Proposal (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - ONR--LISP Machines Proposal (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Bio Medical Knowledge Representation (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - DENDRAL (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Lederberg Material on History of DENDRAL (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - DART (IBM Sponsor) (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Software Request (Example) (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - DARDA Proposal 1982 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Allan Terry--Thesis UC Irvine but under EAF (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Tom Dietterich Thesis Proposal (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Margaret Jacks Hall Building Dedication, 1980; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Computer Science symposium held as part of Margaret Jacks Hall building dedication, 1980; 3 audiocassette(s) (Box 18)
    - AAAS Symposium Machine Intelligence, Past, Present and Future, 1980; 3 audiocassette(s) (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - MSG Manual (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Additional Manual (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - KRL (Knowledge Representation Language) (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - MOLGEN--Notes and Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Stanford Artificial Intelligence Project Papers, Surveys (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - HPP-66-3 Paper--"Logic of Scientific Inquiry" (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - HPP-66-1--Artificial Intelligence Project and Other Papers (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - HPP-62-2--Systematics of Organic Molecules, Graph Topology and Hamilton Circuits (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - HPP-64-1 DENDRAL-64-A System for Computer Construction, Enumeration and Notation of Organic Molecules as Three Structures and Cyclic Graphs (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Lederberg: DENDRAL-64 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Hazen HPP.Summary (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Proposal to ARPA (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - MOLGEN Proposal, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - DENDRAL (Box 21, Folder 10.1)
    - DENDRAL (Box 21, Folder 10.2)
    - ACM (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - "Quo Vadimus: Computer Science in a Decade," June 1980; "Minutes of the Workshop on the Application of Artificial Intelligence to Electronic Warfare," 6 and 7 August 1975 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Computing Reviews (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Australia Conference Transcripts (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Computers and Thought II (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - ARPA UPP Project (Basic Research Grant) (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - PUB Manual, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - EPAM Carnegie Institute of Technology (Box 21, Folder 18.1)
    - EPAM Carnegie Institute of Technology (Box 21, Folder 18.2)
    - Midwest Human Factors Society Symposium on "Human Factors and Computers" (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - AFIPS, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - NCC Program Review, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - ACM Computer Science Conference, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - National Computer Conference and Exposition 1975 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - "Books on Display" ACM Computer Science Conference (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - American Federation of Information Processing Societies Headquarters Newsletter, May/June 1978 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Computer Conference, Los Angeles, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Reprints of Papers Presented at the Computer Conference, Los Angeles, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Proceedings of the Eastern Joint Computer Conference, New York, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Proceedings of the Western Joint Computer Conference, San Francisco, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - LISP, March 1972 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - ARPA Contractors Meeting, January, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - HPP Semiannual Report (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Sridharan, N. S., et al, "A Heuristic Program to Discover Syntheses for Complex Organic Molecules," SAIL Memo Aim-205 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Masinter, L., et al, "Applications of Artificial Intelligence for Chemical Inference XII--Exhaustive Generation of Cyclic and Acyclic Isomers," SAIL Memo Aim-216 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Buchanan, Bruce and N. S. Sridhpm, "Analysis of Behavior of Chemical Molecules: Rule Formation on Non-Homogeneous Classes of Objects," SAIL Memo Aim-215 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Buchanan, Bruce, "Review of Hubert Dreyfus' `What Computers Can't Do': A Critique of Artificial Reason," SAIL Memo Aim-181 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Brown, Harold and Masinter, Larry, "An Algorithm for the Construction of the Graphs of Organic Molecules," STAN-CS-73-361 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - ARPA-HPP Continuation Proposal ARPA Order #3423 (April 1979) (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Articles (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - 2 FCZ 752 ONR N0004-79-C-0302 Guidon (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Bennett, J., et al, "A Knowledge-Based Consultant for Structural Analysis," HPP Sept. 1978 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - HPP--Mathematical Graph Theory (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Lederberg DENDRAL (pre-HPP) (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Callero, Monti, "An Adaptive Commmand and Control System Utilizing Heuristic Learning Processes," SAIL Memo AI-58 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Mark Stefik Thesis (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - ARPA Contractors Meeting, February, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Lenat Thesis (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - CONGEN (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - CONGEN Manual, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - CONGEN (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Heuristic Programming Project 1980 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - HPP Series--Master Listing (not complete) (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - HPP Recent, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Training Program in Biomedical Computing (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Various Proposals (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - NSF, 1972-74 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - NSF Guidelines for Ethical and Human Value Implications of Science and Technology, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - NSF Proposal Reviews (dead Storage) (Sedelow), 1975-76 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - NSF (Input to Congressional Report), 1978 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Pamela McCorduck's Project, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Patent Agreements, 1971-72 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - PDP-6 Usage, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Pharmacology Talk, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - PhD Exam questions, 1962-66 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Predictor.Documentation, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Principal Investigators Conference Dec. 8, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Privacy Report, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Psychology Department, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Production Systems, 1973-74 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Protein Structure Project, circa 1972 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Psych 216, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Psychology Congress--20th International--Japan, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Psychological Abstract (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Public Policy Research Organization, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Publication Policies CSD/ARPA, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Rand, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Rand Corporation--Consulting, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Rand Mailbox, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Rand Consulting, 1969-73 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Report--Dec. 16, 1975 Meeting Rand (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Rand Intelligent Terminals, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Rand/Terrorist Model, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Raub Project, 1967-70 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Recording Equipment Information, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Renderings--8-1/2 x 11 of Lecture Slides (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Research Assistants, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - RFD--Research Development Fund, 1972-73 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Research, General, 1961-65 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Research Information Reports [Stanford], 1969-70 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Reviews [of work by others]--by E. A. F., 1962-73 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Rochester Trip, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - U. C. San Diego Committee, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Security, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Distributed Sens ror Net 10/24-25, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Shaw, David, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Sierra Club Books (1) (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Sierra Club Books (2) (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - SIGCYC (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Sigma Xi, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Slide Drawings (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - SLIP, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - SMSG Project, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Space, 1970-74 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Speech Understanding, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Speech Understanding Systems, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Sridharan, Natesa, 1971-72 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Stanford Land Use, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Stanford Magazine, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Stanford Research Specialties Table, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - Study of Education Committee, 1967-68 (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - SUMEX Correspondence, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - SUMEX/Information Processing Psychology, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - SUMEX Proposal, 1972-74 (Box 23, Folder 58)
    - Summer Law Program, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 59)
    - Suppes Project, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 60)
    - The Fifth Generation: Dawn of the Second Computer Age Internazxtional Conference, London. Sponsored by SPL International. (1 of 5), July 1982 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - The Fifth Generation: Dawn of the Second Computer Age Internazxtional Conference, London. Sponsored by SPL International. (2 of 5), July 1982 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - The Fifth Generation: Dawn of the Second Computer Age Internazxtional Conference, London. Sponsored by SPL International. (3 of 5), July 1982 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - The Fifth Generation: Dawn of the Second Computer Age Internazxtional Conference, London. Sponsored by SPL International. (4 of 5), July 1982 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - The Fifth Generation: Dawn of the Second Computer Age Internazxtional Conference, London. Sponsored by SPL International. (5 of 5), July 1982 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Expert Systems Workshop, San Diego, (1 of 4), Aug. 25-28, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Expert Systems Workshop, San Diego, (2 of 4), Aug. 25-28, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 7)